let questions = [{
        number: 1,
        question: "The Gospel of Mark begins with?",
        answer: "Jesus's baptism by John",
        options: [
            "John the Baptist's Birth",
            "Jesus's Birth",
            "The angel Gabriel appearing to Mary",
            "Jesus's baptism by John"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "John the forerunner of Jesus, Proclaims forgiveness of sins and performs:",
        answer: "Baptisms",
        options: [
            "Circumcisions",
            "Baptisms",
            "Weddings",
            "Miracles"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: "When Jesus is baptized, the spirit of God descends on him in the shape of:",
        answer: "A Dove",
        options: [
            "A Dove",
            "Flames",
            "Angels",
            "A sunbeam"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: "All of the following figures recognize Jesus in Mark except:",
        answer: "John the Baptist",
        options: [
            "The Demons",
            "John the Baptist",
            "The Gentile soldier at the cross",
            "The reader of the Gospel"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: "The phrase 'Jesus Passion' refers to:",
        answer: "Jesus' Suffering",
        options: [
            "Jesus's Birth",
            "Jesus' violent actions in the Temple",
            "Jesus' Love for Humanity",
            "Jesus' Suffering"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "According to Mark, the messiah must:",
        answer: "Suffer and Die",
        options: [
            "Suffer and Die",
            "Preach and Baptize",
            "Become the high Priest",
            "Take control of Israel"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: "In the first-century apocalyptic Judaism, the term 'Son of Man' referred to:",
        answer: "A cosmic figure",
        options: [
            "God's Son",
            "A cosmic figure",
            "The King",
            "The high Priest"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: "At Jesus' trial in Mark, the Sanhedrin charges him with:",
        answer: "Blasphemy",
        options: [
            "Theft",
            "Blasphemy",
            "Being empowered by Satan",
            "Not observing Sabbath laws"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: "In Mark, the Temple curtain rips:",
        answer: "At Jesus' Death",
        options: [
            "At Jesus' Birth",
            "At Jesus' Trial",
            "At Jesus' Death",
            "At Jesus' Resurrection"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: "The Gospel of Mark was probably written around:",
        answer: "65-70 C.E.",
        options: [
            "35-40 C.E",
            "45-50 C.E",
            "55-60 C.E",
            "65-70 C.E."
        ]
    }
];